A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art AAA.doroweig
Archives of American Art
Dorothy Weiss Gallery records
bulk 1984-2000
circa 1964-2001
AAA.doroweig
Archives of American Art
18.7 Linear feet
The records of the Dorothy Weiss Gallery measure 18.7 linear feet and date from circa 1964 to 2001 (bulk 1984-2000). The collection documents the gallery's relationships with approximately three hundred artists, through artist files, exhibition files, and subject files, and is an excellent source of information on the work of contemporary ceramic and glass sculptors.
Dorothy Weiss Gallery
Historical Note
Dorothy Weiss founded the Dorothy Weiss Gallery in 1984. From 1977 Weiss had partnered with Sue Meyer and Virginia Breier in Meyer Breier Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc. She opened her new gallery in what was to be its permanent location at 256 Sutter Street in downtown San Francisco.
The Dorothy Weiss Gallery was renowned in San Francisco for the quality of its crafts program and the artists it represented. Weiss focused on contemporary ceramic and glass sculpture with an emphasis on non-functional, sculptural work. She also showed some paintings, drawings and monotypes, and her interests in this area expanded, particularly in the mid-1990s, when she began exhibiting works by artists such as Daniel Brice, in addition to showing drawings by artists generally known for their sculpture.
Weiss represented many of the country's most prominent and well-respected artists working in glass, including Hank Murta Adams, Dale Chihuly, Richard Marquis, William Morris, Jay Musler, Clifford Rainey, Italo Scanga, Therman Statom, and James Watkins. Glass exhibitions at the gallery included site-specific installations by artists such as Statom, Adams, and Rainey.
The gallery was also an important venue for contemporary ceramists such as Rudy Autio, Annette Corcoran, Ruth Duckworth, Michael Lucero, Beverly Mayeri, and Robert Turner. Monthly exhibitions were held on the Third floor with the Fourth floor gallery space being reserved for a variety of work by gallery artists. "Teapot Invitationals," and exhibitions of "new glass" featuring teapots and glass sculpture by a variety of artists were held regularly at the gallery.
Weiss was an active participant in the wider art community, hosting collector's groups from around the country and guests during conferences, such as a special Glass Invitational in conjunction with the Glass Art Society Conference in March 1994. As a member of the San Francisco Art Dealers Association (SFADA), Weiss participated in First Thursday, holding opening receptions to new exhibitions on the first Thursday of every month and often accompanying them with artists' talks. She also participated in an annual Introductions show along with other SFADA members, representing younger, emerging artists in the Bay Area and nationwide. In addition, Weiss assisted the American Craft Museum in developing its exhibition programs, and was a Collectors Circle Affiliate for the American Craft Council.
Dorothy Weiss closed the gallery in 2000, retiring at the age of eighty. On October 4 of that year the Museum of Craft and Folk Art in San Francisco opened A Tribute to Dorothy Weiss, an exhibition selected from her own collection.
Scope and Content Note
The Dorothy Weiss Gallery records measure 18.7 linear feet and date from circa 1964 to 2001 (bulk 1984-2000). Although the collection includes limited records overlapping from Weiss's dealings with some artists through Meyer Breier Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., its primary focus is the activities of the Dorothy Weiss Gallery. The records provide fairly extensive coverage of the gallery's relationship with approximately thirty artists, and scattered documentation of Weiss's relationship with more than two hundred other artists whose work she represented, exhibited, or had an interest in at some time during the gallery's existence. Overall, the collection is an excellent source of information on contemporary ceramic and glass sculpture and includes artist files of correspondence, administrative records, printed matter, and photographic material, as well as exhibition files and subject files.
The bulk of the collection consists of Series 1: Artist Files, which includes correspondence with artists, biographical material, printed material relating to exhibitions at the Dorothy Weiss Gallery and elsewhere, photographs of artwork, and administrative records such as price lists, inventories, and loan and consignment documentation.
Series 2: Exhibition Files contains records of approximately twenty-five group exhibitions held at the gallery, such as the Teapot Invitationals, and various exhibitions of glass artists. Records relating to exhibitions for a single artist's work can be found in Series 1: Artist Files.
Series 3: Subject Files consists of a small group of general subject files maintained by the gallery, such as correspondence with different types of clients, and records relating to specific projects outside the gallery in which Weiss participated.
See Index for List of Exhibitions at Meyer Breir Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., and the Dorothy Weiss Gallery.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series. The basic original arrangement was maintained throughout the collection. Records are generally arranged alphabetically by artist, subject, or exhibition, and then chronologically.
Series 1: Artist Files, circa 1964-2001(boxes 1-18, OV 21; 17.5 linear ft.)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1979-1999 (box 19; 0.75 linear ft.)
Series 3: Subject Files, 1983-2000 (boxes 19-20; 0.45 linear ft.)
Index: List of Exhibitions
Below is a list of exhibitions held at Meyer Breir Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., and the Dorothy Weiss Gallery from 1980 to 2000. Italics indicate the actual title of the exhibition. Every effort has been made to include all known exhibitions.
Date Exhibition
Oct. 14-Nov. 15, 1980 David Kuraoka - Clay
Nov. 18-Dec. 24, 1980 Functional Forms
Mar. 17-Apr. 11, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series I
Apr. 14-May 9, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series II
May 12-June 6, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series III
Sept. 15-Oct. 17, 1981 Joyce Kohl - Clay Sculpture; Gayle Luchessa - Felting
Apr. 6-May 15, 1982 David Gilhooly
May 25-June 26, 1982 Philip Cornelius
July 6-Aug. 7, 1982 Painted Object
Mar. 1-Apr. 2, 1983 Buildings
Apr. 5-May 14, 1983 Teapots
May 31-July 9, 1983 Neil Williams - An Explanation of the Vessel
July 30-Sept. 3, 1983 David Gilhooly
Feb. 7-Mar. 3, 1984 Roseline Delisle - Porcelain; Walter Lieberman - Glass
Apr. 3-28, 1984 Jay Kvapil, Sculpture - Domestic Monuments Series
May 1-June 2, 1984 Stan Welsh, Recent Works - Ceramic Sculpture and Monotypes
Aug. 30-Sept. 22, 1984 Philip Cornelius - New Work, Porcelain Vessels
Sept. 25-Oct. 27, 1984 Jamie Walker - Ceramic Work and Installation
Nov. 1-24, 1984 Yoshio Taylor - Clay Sculpture
Nov. 28-Dec. 31, 1984 The Teapot
Feb. 5-Mar. 2, 1985 Neil Williams - Recent Work in Clay
Mar. 5-30, 1985 Scott Chamberlin - New Clay Sculpture
Apr. 2-27, 1985 Hank Murta Adams - Glass Sculpture
Apr. 30-Jun. 1, 1985 Allan Winkler - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture and Paper Cut-outs
June 6-July 6, 1985 Glass Sculpture - Five Artists
July 12-Aug. 4, 1985 Group show
Aug. 6-31, 1985 Linda Einfalt - Sculpture; Tom Heid - Ceramic Sculpture
Aug. 8-Sept. 1, 1985 Jamie Walker
Sept. 5-28, 1985 Louis Marak, Kazuko Matthews - Ceramic Sculpture
Sept. 15-29, 1985 Philip Cornelius
Oct. 3-Nov. 2, 1985 Rudy Autio - Ceramic Sculpture
Nov. 5-30, 1985 Juta Savage - Recent Work, Sculpture and Porcelain
Dec. 5-Jan. 4, 1985-86 Roseline Delisle - Recent Work in Porcelain and Drawings
Feb. 6-28, 1986 British Ceramics
Mar. 6-29, 1986 Jamie Walker - Ceramic Work
April, 1986 Jay Kvapil - Sculpture
April, 1986 Hitoshi Sasaki - Wall Sculptures
Apr. 29-May 31, 1986 Rick Dillingham - Recent Work
June 3-July 5, 1986 Stan Welsh - Ceramic Sculpture, Monotypes
June 11-July 4, 1986 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
July 12-Aug. 2, 1986 Barbara Bell Smith - Paintings
Sept. 11-Oct. 4, 1986 Philip Cornelius - Porcelain Vessels
Oct. 9-Nov. 1, 1986 Tony Hepburn - New Sculpture
Nov. 5-29, 1986 Yoshio Taylor - Figurative Sculpture
Dec. 2-Jan. 3, 1986-87 Teapots - New Boundaries
Jan. 8-31, 1987 Todd Pearson - New Sculpture
Feb. 5-28, 1987 Jack Bowers - New Boxes
Mar. 3-28, 1987 Louis Marak - New Sculpture
Mar. 31-Apr. 25, 1987 Scott Chamberlin - "A Different Garden," Sculpture and Drawings
Apr. 30-May 23, 1987 Robert Turner
May 26-June 9, 1987 Amy Podmore - Figurative Sculpture
June 11-July 8, 1987 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture, Glass and Bronze
June 11-Aug. 8, 1987 Introductions - Amy Podmore, Michio Sugiyama
Aug. 11-Sept. 5, 1987 Diane Olivier - Drawings
Sept., 1987 Nancy Carman
Oct. 8-31, 1987 Rudy Autio - Ceramic Sculpture
Nov. 5-28, 1987 Roseline Delisle - New Work
Dec., 1987 Group Glass Exhibition
Jan. 7-30, 1988 Joseph Slusky - New Sculpture
Feb. 2-Feb. 27, 1988 Linda Einfalt, Jaap Bongers - Recent Sculpture
Feb. 5-Mar. 28, 1998 Potent Images - Figurative Clay Sculpture
Mar. 3-Apr. 2, 1988 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture and Drawings
Apr. 7-30, 1988 Jamie Walker - New Work
May 5-28, 1988 Stan Welsh - New Sculpture
June 9-July 2, 1988 Philip Cornelius - New Work
July 5-30, 1988 Introductions: Tim Mosman - Sculpture and Paintings; Marc Pandone - Drawings
Aug. 4-Sept. 3, 1988 Allan Winkler - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture and Paper Cut-outs
Sept. 8-Oct. 1, 1988 Barbara Bell Smith - New Paintings
Oct. 6-29, 1988 Jun Kaneko - New Work
Nov. 3-26, 1988 Yoshio Taylor - New Ceramic Sculpture
Dec. 1-Jan. 7, 1989 Annette Corcoran - New Work
Jan. 5-31, 1989 1989 - New Work for the New Year
Feb. 2-28, 1989 Diane Olivier - New Drawings
Mar. 2-Apr. 1, 1989 Amy Podmore - Recent Work
Apr. 6-May 3, 1989 Ruth Duckworth - New Work
May 4-31, 1989 The Alfred Show - Professors and Graduates Associated with Alfred University
June 8-July 6, 1989 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
July 8-Aug. 1, 1989 Introductions 1989: Deborah Hoch - Narrative Clay; Lisa Reinertson - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture
Sept. 7-Oct. 3, 1989 Scott Chamberlin - New Sculpture
Oct. 5-31, 1989 Rudy Autio - New Sculpture
Nov. 2-Dec. 2, 1989 James Morris - Narrative Sculpture
Dec. 7-30, 1989 New Glass
Jan. 4-27, 1990 1990 - New Work for the New Year by Gallery Artists
Feb. 1-27, 1990 Louis Marak - New Work
Mar. 1-31, 1990 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
Apr. 5-28, 1990 John Gill - New Work
May 3-June 30, 1990 Jack Earl - Narrative Sculpture
July 5-Aug. 5, 1990 Steve Briscoe - Introductions
Aug. 9-Sept. 1, 1990 Teapot Invitational
Sept. 6-Oct. 6, 1990 Jamie Walker - New Work
Oct. 11-Nov. 3, 1990 Jun Kaneko - New Sculpture
Nov. 8-Dec. 1, 1990 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture
Dec. 6-31, 1990 Annette Corcoran - New Work
Jan. 10-Feb. 2, 1991 Sculpture 1991
Feb. 7-Mar. 2, 1991 Stan Welsh - New Work
Mar. 7-30, 1991 Yoshio Taylor - New Sculpture
Apr. 4-27, 1991 Barbara Bell Smith - Recent Paintings
May 2-June 1, 1991 Michael Lucero - New Work
June 6-29, 1991 New Sculpture - Hank Murta Adams, Pike Powers, Michael Scheiner, James Watkins
July 3-27, 1991 Introductions '91: Jeremy Popelka - Glass Sculpture; Sana Krusoe - Ceramic Sculpture
Aug. 1-31, 1991 New Glass
Sept. 5-28, 1991 Diane Olivier - Works on Paper
Oct. 3-Nov. 2, 1991 Robert Turner - Master Works in Clay
Nov. 7-30, 1991 James Morris - New Sculpture and Drawings
Dec. 5-Jan. 11, 1991-92 Teapot Invitational
Feb. 6-29, 1992 John Gill - New Sculpture
Mar. 5-28, 1992 Beveryly Mayeri - New Ceramic Sculpture
Apr. 2-May 2, 1992 Hank Murta Adams - Glass Sculpture
May 7-30, 1992 Ruth Duckworth - Recent Work
June 4-27, 1992 Jack Earl - New Narrative Sculpture
July 2-Aug. 1, 1992 Introductions
Aug. 6-29, 1992 Therman Statom - New Sculpture, Glass Houses, Ladders, and Wall Pieces
Sept. 3-26, 1992 Jamie Walker - New Sculpture
Oct. 1-31, 1992 Jun Kaneko - Recent Sculpture
Nov. 5-28, 1992 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture and Drawings
Dec. 3-Jan. 2, 1992-93 Annette Corcoran - Figurative Teapots
Dec. 5-Jan. 11, 1992-93 Teapot Invitational
Jan. 7-39, 1993 Robert Kehlmann - Drawings with Glass
Feb. 4-27, 1993 The Clay Figure
March 4-27, 1993 Glass Invitational
Apr. 1-May 1, 1993 James Morris - Ceramic Sculpture, Paintings and Drawings
May 6-29, 1993 Teapot Invitational
June 3-July 3, 1993 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
July 10-31, 1993 Introductions '93 - Daniel Goldstein, Metal Sculpture with Movement and Light
Sept. 9-Oct. 2, 1993 Robin Grebe, James Watkins - Recent Works in Glass
Oct. 7-30, 1993 Recent Sculpture - Rudy Autio, Jim Leedy
Nov. 4-27, 1993 Mark Lindquist - Recent Works
Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 1993-94 Clifford Rainey - New Sculpture, Drawings and Installation
Feb. 3-26, 1994 Clay Selections
Mar. 3-Apr. 2, 1994 Glass Invitational
Apr. 7-30, 1994 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
May 5-28, 1994 William Morris - New Sculpture
June 2-July 2, 1994 John Gill, Louis Marak - Recent Work
July 7-30, 1994 Introductions '94 - Lawrence LaBianca, Gregory Roberts
Aug. 4-27, 1994 Teapot Invitational
Sept. 8-Oct 1, 1994 Ruth Duckworth - Recent Sculpture
Oct. 6-29, 1994 Michael Lucero - Dogs and Children
Nov. 3-26, 1994 Jun Kaneko - Recent Work
Dec. 1-Jan. 7, 1994-95 Annette Corcoran - New Work, A Bird in the Hand
Jan. 14-Feb. 25, 1995 Therman Statom - Northern Tide - Site-Specific Installation and Other Works
Mar. 2-Apr. 1, 1995 Stan Welsh - New Work
Apr. 6-29, 1995 Daniel Brice, David Tomb - Recent Drawings
May 4-27, 1995 Jack Earl - Narrative Sculpture
June 1-July 1, 1995 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
July 6-29, 1995 Introductions' 95 - Timothy Hower, Helene E. C. Linder
Aug. 3-Sept 2, 1995 Horse Show
Sept. 7-30, 1995 Charles Hobson: Clouds & Dreams - Variations on Longitude and Surrealism
Oct. 5-29, 1995 New Clay - Jeff Irwin, Annabeth Rosen
Nov. 2-Dec. 2, 1995 Jay Musler - Imaginary Evolution
Dec. 7-Jan. 27, 1995-96 Teapot Invitational
Feb. 1-Mar. 2, 1996 Jun Kaneko - Drawings and Sculpture
Mar. 7-30, 1996 Daniel Brice, Philip Cornelius and James Morris
Apr. 4-27, 1996 Beveryly Mayeri - New Work
May 2-June 1, 1996 Michael Lucero - Reclamation Series
June 6-29, 1996 Jim Melchert and Jamie Walker - "Affinities," Sculpture for the Garden
July 5-Aug. 3, 1996 Introductions '96 - Masako Miyata, Jenifer Wofford
Sept. 5-28, 1996 Hank Murta Adams, Pike Powers, James Watkins - Glass Sculpture
Oct. 3-Nov. 30, 1996 Gregory Roberts - Thirst
Nov. 7-30, 1996 Dog Show
Dec. 5-Feb. 1, 1996-97 Annette Corcoran - Icones Avium
Feb. 6-Mar. 1, 1997 Scott Chamberlin, Annabeth Rosen, Arnie Zimmerman
Mar. 6-Apr., 26, 1997 Therman Statom - Myths, Science and Nature
May 1-31, 1997 Doug Jeck - Men and Boys
June 5-July 5, 1997 Sculptors and Their Drawings - Rudy Autio, Jun Kaneko, & Michael Lucero
July 10-Aug. 2, 1997 Introductions '97 - Sean Fletcher, Patrick Hilferty, Cassandra Jones, Beth King
Aug. 7-30, 1997 Chris Silliman, Sergei Isupov - New Clay
Sept. 4-27, 1997 Charles Hobson: Lighthouse Legends - Works on Paper and Artist's Books
Oct. 2-Nov. 29, 1997 Clifford Rainey - "Homo Faber," New Sculpture
Dec. 4-Jan. 31, 1997-98 Teapot Invitational
Feb. 5-Mar. 28, 1998 Potent Images - Figurative Clay Sculpture
Apr. 2-May 2, 1998 Beveryly Mayeri - The Nature Series
May 7-June 27, 1998 Jun Kaneko - New Work
July 9-Aug. 1, 1998 Introductions '98 - Elizabeth Ennis, Susan L. Howard, Dharma Strasser
Aug. 6-28, 1998 The Dimensional Canvas - Painted Studio Glass
Sept. 3-25, 1998 New Work From Europe - Wouter Dam and Ken Eastman
Oct. 1-31, 1998 Richard Marquis - New Work
Nov. 5-28, 1998 Daniel Brice - New Work on Paper
Dec. 3-Jan. 30, 1998-99 Annette Corcoran - New Work
Jan. 7-30, 1999 Important Works in Clay and Glass
Feb. 4-27, 1999 Justin Hunter - Recent Paintings and Drawings; Lawrence LaBianca - Reconnection With Nature
Mar. 4-27, 1999 Annabeth Rosen - New Work
Apr. 1-30, 1999 Philip Cornelius - New Work
May 6-29, 1999 Doug Jeck - Recent Sculpture
June 3-30, 1999 Jean-Pierre Larocque - New Work
July 8-31, 1999 Introductions '99 - David King, Barbara Hashimoto
Aug. 5-31, 1999 Stephen Bradford - Figurative Sculpture, William Samios - New Paintings
Sept. 9-Oct. 30, 1999 Michael Lucero - Wonderland Series
Nov. 4-30, 1999 Steven Montgomery - Recent Sculpture
Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 1999-00 Therman Statom - New Glass Sculpture
Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 2000 Teapot Invitational
Feb. 3-29, 2000 Sergei Isupov, Gregory Roberts - New Sculpture
Mar. 2-31, 2000 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
Apr. 6-29, 2000 Daniel Brice - Drawings
Mar. 2-May 20, 2000 Gallery Closing Sale
Provenance
The collection was donated to the Archives of American Art by Dorothy Weiss in 2002.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. research facility.
Breier, Virginia, 1927-; Meyer Breyer Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc.; Meyer, Sue, 1913-; Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America; Weiss, Dorothy, 1921-; Art galleries, Commercial--California--San Francisco; Ceramic sculpture; Ceramicists; Glass artists; Glass sculpture; Handicraft--California; Handicraft--Exhibitions
- Artist Files, circa 1964-2001; Series 1; 17.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-18, OV 21
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains files for artists represented by the gallery, or featured in the gallery's exhibitions. There are also files for artists in whom Weiss had an interest but with whom she never pursued a business relationship. While some artists are represented by only a single file, others are represented more fully. The latter include Hank Murta Adams, Rudy Autio, Annette Corcoran, Philip Cornelius, Wouter Dam, Ruth Duckworth, Jack Earl, Tony Hepburn, Jun Kaneko, Michael Lucero, Beverly Mayeri, William Morris, Jay Musler, Barbara Bell Smith, Statom Therman, Yoshio Taylor, Robert Turner, Jamie Walker, and Stan Welsh.
  Files typically include any or all of the following: announcements and press releases for exhibitions held at the gallery; correspondence with artists, buyers, collectors, museums and art institutions; biographical material such as résumés and artist statements; consignment, loan and shipping records; inventories and price lists; printed material; photographs of artists; and photographs of artwork.
  Correspondence generally includes original incoming letters and drafts or copies of outgoing letters. To preserve the original order of the collection, records relating to a particular artist were broken down according to the system imposed by the creator. Consequently, files labeled "correspondence" may also include material such as price lists, inventories, consignment and loan records, invoices, and shipping records.
  Photographic material generally consists of images of artwork and may also contain images of gallery installations or photographs of work in an artist's studio. Photographs of artists are filed separately and/or noted in the container list.
  Additional slide transparencies of artwork by many of the artists represented here can be found at the end of the series. These were separated from the artist files in which they were originally housed for storage reasons. Researchers should check the list of transparencies for additional information about any artist of interest. "SB" next to the box number indicates the slide box in which particular slide transparencies are housed.
  Arrangement note
  Files are arranged alphabetically by artist. When there is more than one folder for an artist they are arranged alphabetically by folder title, with the exception of photographs of artists and photographic material which are placed at the end of each group. Transparencies of artwork are arranged alphabetically by artists, and chronologically by date of artwork (not the date that the transparency was developed which is often unknown), with undated transparencies at the beginning of each group.
  - Abilgard, Mark (Box 1)
    - General, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Printed Material, 1989-1998, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abright, Bill, General, 1987-1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Hank Murta (Box 1)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1985-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Collector Records, 1993-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Loan Forms, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Shipping Records, 1989-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Adams, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1981-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - Aebersold, Jane Ford, General, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alexandrov, Simona, General, circa 1994-1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anderson, Daniel, General, 1987-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Marvin, General, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Andreson, Laura, General, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arima, Curtis, General, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arleo, Adrian, General, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Autio, Rudy (Box 1)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1985-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1995, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Collector Records, 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Consignment Records (other galleries), 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28-31)
    - Correspondence, Gallery Koyanagi, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - Shipping Records, 1987-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Photographs of Autio, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Photographic Material, 1980s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Photographic Material, cont., 1980s-1990s (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Balas, Jack, General, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bartneck, Lea and Richard Marquis, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bean, Kevin, General, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Berman, Harriete Estel, General, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bermudez, Luis, General, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Blakely, Ellen, General, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bongers, Jaap (Box 2)
    - General, 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bowers, Jack, General, circa 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bradford, Steven P., General, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Braun, Stephen, General, circa 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brice, Daniel, General, 1991-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bright, Erik, General, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Briscoe, Steve (Box 2)
    - General, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Britt, John, General, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Brook-Kothlow, Ingrid, General, circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Burleson, Mark, General, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Carlson, Robert, circa 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Carman, Nancy (Box 2)
    - General, 1982-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1973-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cartwright, Virginia, General, 1981-1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Castle, Wendell, General, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Caswell, James, Photographic Material, circa 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cecula, Marek, General, circa 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlin, Scott (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1997 (Box 2, Folder 28-31)
    - Printed Material, 1980-1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chardiet, Jose, General, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Chihuly, Dale (Box 2)
    - General, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Christenson, Ann, General, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Chung, Sam, General, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clayman, Daniel, General, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)